chiff.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Statement for Users of the Chiff.com Internet Directory

Privacy Policy

A Guide to What Personal Information We Collect  
and How We Use and Protect Your Information

Protecting your privacy and safeguarding your personal information is one of our highest priorities. 

The following Privacy Statement explains how Chiff.com collects and protects your information. If you have any questions that are not covered by this statement, please contact us at [support@chiff.com](mailto:support@chiff.com?subject=Privacy). 

By using Chiff.com Web, you give your consent to the collection and use of certain personal information. Please look over the following FAQ to learn more. 

**_Why do we gather information?_** Statistics and demographics are topics that our advertisers want to see. That's a reality both online and off. But... knowing who uses this site helps us provide better service to you. We are not interested in anyone's individual information, but if most of our visitors are nearing retirement age - we may want to provide more in depth information on those issues. If more visitors are college aged, financial aid and job prospects would be more useful. Young parent's may be concerned with saving for their kids to go to college. You can see the connection between who you are and what we focus on.

**_What information do we collect?_** Chiff.com does not collect personal information as you visit the site, nor does it store or othewise record any e-mail addresses when you sign up for our free newsletter. However, we do carry ads and other third party links that may add cookies to your computer to obtain information. 

**_Do we share the information collected with any other third parties?_** We do share information with our newsletter service, however we have reviewed their policy in regard to client's information and it is in line with our philosophy. In the event that their policy changes, we will find another service or produce the newsletters in-house.

**_Does our Privacy Statement apply to the sites to which we link?_** We cannot state that all of the sites we link to have the same policies. However, one of the criteria for site selection we look for is whether we, as consumers of their products or information, are treated with the dignity and respect that we deserve. It is our belief that a site with questionable ethics cannot be trusted to provide reliable information or to protect us from predatory advertisers. We feel it is our responsibility to exercise our right to choose not to sanction these activities. 

_**What about "cookies" and other tracking devices?**_ Cookies are actually very helpful to the consumer when they are used ethically. Cookies allow your bank, for example, to recognize you and allow you to set up accounts at stores and other online services. Again, it is the misuse of cookies by the unethical that causes problems. If you set your cookies to only allow those that are sent back to the originator, it will probably offer some protection. However, misuse of cookies and abuse of e-mail are issues that the Internet community needs to find answers for. 

As stated above, we do not set cookies. However, that does not limit our advertising and social media partners from doing so. 

**IMPORTANT NOTE:** For more information see: [How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/). Also see [AddThis](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy), our social media partner, for more on their privacy policy with additional instructions on how to opt out entirely.

In the event of a change in our policy, a revised Privacy Statement will promptly be posted to this Web site. You agree to accept posting of a revised Privacy Statement electronically on the web site as actual notice to you. You should review the Privacy Statement periodically to remain informed of any changes.

In summary, we respect your right to privacy and will do whatever we can to make sure that those we deal with have the same philosophy on paper and in action.
